A Guide to the Will M. Myers papers FA042
Rockefeller Archive Center
Will M. Myers papers
1946-1970
Rockefeller Archive Center
Myers, Will M.
Rockefeller Foundation
FA042
10.19 Cubic Feet 13 letter document cases; 11 legal document cases
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
The Will M. Myers Papers collection is arranged in eight series:
Series 1 - History
Series 2 - Grasslands Conferences
Series 3 - International Institutes of Agriculture
Series 4 - Speeches and Reprints
Series 5 - Memorabilia and Awards
Series 6 - Reprints
Series 7 - Accession 53
Series 1014 - Photographs
Biographical/Historical note
Will Martin Myers (1911-1970) was born and raised in Bancroft, Kansas. He received a B.S. in Agronomy from Kansas State College in 1932 and an M.S. and Ph.D. in Plant Genetics from the University of Minnesota in 1934 and 1936.
In 1937 Dr. Myers joined the United States Department of Agriculture as Geneticist at the Pasture Research Laboratory, State College, Pennsylvania. After World War II he was Geneticist and Consultant with the Far Eastern Command in Japan. He returned to the USDA as Head of the Division of Forage Crops and Diseases and then as Director of Field Crops Research at Beltsville, Maryland. From 1950-1952 Dr. Myers organized the Sixth International Grasslands Conference and later was Chairman of the U.S. Delegation to the Seventh International Grasslands Conference in 1956. After leaving the Department of Agriculture in 1952, Dr. Myers became Head of the Department of Agronomy and Plant Genetics at the University of Minnesota. He became Dean of the Office of International Programs in 1963.
Dr. Myers had been a consultant to The Rockefeller Foundation since 1954 and spent 1959-1960 in India in that capacity. As Associate Director of Agricultural Sciences in 1964 he also became Director of the International Institute of Tropical Agriculture in Ibadan from 1965-1967. With the Institute formally organized in 1968, he became Chairman of the Board. In 1967 Dr. Myers became Vice-President of the Foundation with interests in the areas of Medical and Natural Sciences, Agriculture, and programs oriented toward University Development, Population, Conquest of Hunger, and Quality of the Environment.
Dr. Myers had many associations, some of which were Chairman, Committee on Agricultural Science, USDA; Chairman, Agricultural Research Facilities Needs Committee, USDA; Chairman, Latin American Science Board National Academy of Sciences; Member, U.S. National Commission, United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO); Consultant, Ford Foundation; Consultant, Office of Science and Technology, Executive Office of the President; Science Advisor to Assistant Administrator, Latin American Bureau, AID and Coordinator, Alliance for Progress, 1962; Member, U.S. Delegation to the United Nations Conference on Application of Science and Technology in Assistance to Developing Nations, 1963; Chairman, Crops Division, 1946, Vice President 1957, President 1958, American Society of Agronomy.
Scope and Contents note
Important subjects covered in this collection include agronomy, ecology, population, genetics and plant breeding, agricultural development of underdeveloped nations, agricultural research institutes, grasslands and Grasslands Conferences.
Important correspondents are W. M. Myers, A. M. Boyce, Arthur Leach, and J. Robert Mitchell.
Related Archival Materials note
See also files in the Rockefeller Foundation Archives pertaining to agriculture, in particular those of the International Institute of Tropical Agriculture.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 2A 19 and IV 2A 21
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Mrs. W. M. Myers deposited Series 1-6 of the W. M. Myers collection with The Rockefeller Foundation Archives on October 21, 1970. Series 7 was received from the Rockefeller Foundation through Records Management and Library Service on July 21, 1977.
Ecology; Grasslands; Population; Environmental sciences; Developing countries; Genetics; Plant breeding; Agriculture -- Research; Agriculture; Agronomy
- History, 1941-1970; 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes subject files as well as course notes, diaries, manuscripts, committee notes, and clippings.
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, Tohoku, Japan (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - All India Institute of Medical Research (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biography (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Agricultural Science, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Agricultural Research Priorities for Economic Development in Africa #1-2, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Agricultural Research Priorities for Economic Development in Africa #3-4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Conference on Agricultural Research Priorities for Economic Development in Africa #5-6, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Agricultural Research Priorities for Economic Development in Africa #7, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Agricultural Research Priorities for Economic Development in Africa #8, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Conference on Agricultural Research Priorities for Economic Development in Africa #9-11, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Diary, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Diary, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Diary, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Flax - Ph.D. Dissertation (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Genetic Control of Physiology Processes in Higher Plants, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Genetic Group, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Genetics Seminar, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "Green Gold", 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - D. D. Hill, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Invitations (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Japan, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Latin American Science Board - Task Force, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Latin American Science Board - Task Force Report (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Manuscript (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Manuscript (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Methods of Plant Breeding, 1941-1957 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Methods of Plant Breeding, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Methods of Plant Breeding - Study Questions, Exams, Bibliography (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Methods of Plant Breeding - Outlines (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) Summer Conference on Agriculture and Underdeveloped Countries, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Orientation Program, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - "Plant Breeding" and "Agriculture" by H. H. Hadley (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Quantitative Genetics, Spring 1958 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Quantitative Inheritance Seminar (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Scandinavia, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Symposium on Mutations in Plant Breeding, Ithaca, November 28-December 2, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - United Nations Conference on the Application of Science and Technology, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - United Nations Education Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) - U. S. National Commission, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Universidad del Valle, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Universidad del Valle, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Universidad del Valle, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Universidad del Valle - Reports (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Universidad del Valle - Reports (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Universidad del Valle - Reports (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Grasslands Conferences, 1948-1960; 2
  This series consists mainly of the organizational papers for the Sixth International Grasslands Conference held at Pennsylvania State College in 1952.
  - 5th International Grasslands Conference, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Announcements & Publicity (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Burcalow, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Committee Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Congress Committees, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - General Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - General Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Invitations (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Location, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, June 1951-April 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, April 16-June 1952 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, April 16-June 1952 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, April 16-June 1952 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Committee Correspondence, April 16-June 1952 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Suggestions (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Suggestions (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Suggestions (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Program Suggestions (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Sections (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Sectional Program Outlines (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Subcommittee Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Working Group, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Pamphlets (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 6th International Grasslands Conference - Tours (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 7th International Grasslands Conference, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 8th International Grasslands Conference, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- International Institutes of Agriculture, 1966-1970; 3
  This series is a listing of meetings and notes concerning the Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT), CIMMYT, International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), and International Rice Research Institute (IRRI).
  - Agricultural Research Institute Meeting, May 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - International Rice Research Institute, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Speeches and Reprints, 1950-1970; 4
  This series is comprised of W. M. Myers's speeches and reprints.
  - "Adjustments in Land Use and Crop Production - Looking Ahead" (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Advanced Studies in Agronomy - Crop Rotation" (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Agronomic Aspects of Dairy Feed Production" (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Are Forage Crops Needed in Corn Belt Agriculture?", 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "The Challenge Agriculture Faces", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Cheap Seed is Expensive" (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Development of the Basic Plant Sciences" (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "The Education of an Agricultural Specialist", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Fifty Years of Progress in Field Crops", 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "The Fight Against Hunger", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Forage Crop Breeding", 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Forage Crops in Agriculture", 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Farm Replanning for Profit", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Grasses and Grass Silage", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Grassland Farming" (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Grassland Management - Pastures", 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Grassland Management for Increased Production in the Humid Areas and Under Irrigation" (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Grassland Potentials and the Grassland Program", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Grassland Research at Rosemont" (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Importance of Research at the University of Minnesota" (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Improved Crop Varieties and Seed Certification", 1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Intensive Grassland Farming Requires Planning for Flexibility" (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "International Dimensions in Education", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "The International Institute of Tropical Agriculture" (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "National Foundation Seed Project", 1951 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "The Need for Grassland Improvement", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "A New Dimension for the University - International Programs", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "The Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) Certification Scheme", 1962 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Our Daily Bread", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "Our Greatest Feed Resource" (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "Pasture Improvement" (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "People, Technology and the Environment", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "The Place of the International Research Centers in the Network" (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "The Plant Breeder Is Greatly Adding to the Nutritional and Economic Value of Grassland Crops" (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "Problems in International Development", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "The Pursuit of Excellence", 1961 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "Raising the Curtain on Research Opportunities" (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - "Research Needs of the Grassland Opportunities" (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Responsibilities of the Research Worker" (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "Role of Mutations in Plant Breeding - Discussion" (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "The Sixth International Grassland Congress", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - "Superior Forage Crop Seeds Are Critical Materials" (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "Summary of Talk Made at Extension Conference Dinner" (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - "Unfinished Business", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - "What It Is Like to Breed a New Variety" (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - "Where Do We Go From Here in Seed Certification?" (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - "Whose Job Is It?" (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "World Food Population Problem, an Overview", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - "Why Do We Need More Agricultural Research?" (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Reprints (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Memorabilia and Awards, 1959-1961; 5
  Scope and Contents
  Included in this series are:
  Senior Judging Contest 1930 Trophy
  Students Crop Judging Contest 1930 Trophy
  Students Crop Judging Contest 1931 Trophy
  Conditions Governing Access
  Due to the oversize nature and potentially brittle condition of this material, special arrangements may be required in order to view materials. Individual items may be restricted due to preservation concerns.
  - Awards (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bancroft High School - Kansas State College (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Passports (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Testimonials (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minnesota Premier Seed Grower, 1961 (Box 1, Folder A)
  - Royal Thai Mint Set (Box 1, Folder B)
  - Thai Shawl (Box 1, Folder C)
  - Map of West Africa. Printed at the survey of Ghana at Accra., 1959; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Folder 1)
    File Plan note
    M-2
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Retrieval times for maps and flat files may exceed 24 hours. Individual items may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
  - Road Map of Nigeria., 1960; MAP (Quantity 1) (Folder 1, Folder 8)
    M-1
- Reprints, 6
  - Africa (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Agricultural Developments - Mimeographs, Reprints, Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Agricultural Developments - Mimeographs, Reprints, Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 0002A)
  - Environment (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation-Agency for International Development (CIC-AID) Rural Development Research Project (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Food (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Genetics (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - India (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Japan (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Population (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rice (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rice (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Virology (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Wheat (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - General (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Accession 53, 1966-1970; 7
  This series contains correspondence, notes, papers, and speeches received from the Rockefeller Foundation through Records Management and Library Service; this material was added to the existing W. M. Myers collection in 1977.
  - Conference on Agricultural Development, Villa Serbelloni, April 23-25, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Summary prepared by W. M. Myers.
  - Conference on Population, Villa Serbelloni, April 6-8, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, papers, notes. Includes "Personal Observations Regarding Population Conference, Villa Serbelloni, April 6-8, 1970" by John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Economic Development Institute, International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, Agricultural Projects Course, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes paper "Agricultural Research" presented by W. M. Myers, August 5, 1968.
  - International Centre for Theoretical Physics, International Atomic Energy Agency - Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Administrative material 1966. Correspondence, notes, printed material.
  - International Rice Research Institute, Department of Agricultural Economics (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Bibliography, April 1967. Paper, "An Analysis of the Interrelationships between Land Preparation and Weeding in Lowland Rice." 1967.
  - Papers and Speeches by W. M. Myers (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Abstract of the Talk Presented at the Meeting of the Association of Southern Agricultural Workers, Mobile, Alabama, February 4, 1969.
    "Hunger - A Challenge to World Agriculture," presented at the Fortieth National Convention of the Alpha Gamma Rho Fraternity, Lincoln, Nebraska, August 26, 1968.
    "Population and Food," presented to the Committee on Foreign Affairs, House of Representatives, Congress of the United States, April 24, 1968. These remarks are largely drawn from an address by J. G. Harrar entitled "Crisis in Human Ecology" before the National Academy of Sciences on April 23, 1968.
    "The Role of Agricultural Sciences in the War on Hunger," presented at the 100th Annual Meeting of the Kansas Academy of Science, Lawrence, Kansas, May 2-4, 1968.
    "Science and Pollution," undated and unidentified paper.
  - Personal (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, Foundation and personal business, 1965-1966.
    Notes, some handwritten, undated. Subjects include the Rockefeller Foundation's University Development program, the University of Brasilia, world agricultural development.
    Outline, "Evolution and Revolution in Agriculture" initialed SW (Sterling Wortman?), no date.
    Memorial, by Harold E. Myers, brother of W. M. Myers, no date.
  - Quality of the Environment - Rockefeller Foundation Program Statements, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - United Nations Advisory Committee on the Application of Science and Technology to Development - Seminar with North American Scientists on Links with Developing Countries, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, notes, printed material.
  - University of the Philippines (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Material relating to visit, September 24-29, 1967.
- Will M. Myers photographs, 1014; 0.3 Cubic Feet; 2 folders; 53 prints
  Biographical / Historical
  Will Martin Myers (1911-1970) was born and raised in Bancroft, Kansas. He received a B.S. in Agronomy from Kansas State College in 1932 and an M.S. and Ph.D. in Plant Genetics from the University of Minnesota in 1934 and 1936.
  In 1937 Dr. Myers joined the United States Department of Agriculture as Geneticist at the Pasture Research Laboratory, State College, Pennsylvania. After World War II he was Geneticist and Consultant with the Far Eastern Command in Japan. He returned to the USDA as Head of the Division of Forage Crops and Diseases and then as Director of Field Crops Research at Beltsville, Maryland. From 1950-1952 Dr. Myers organized the Sixth International Grasslands Conference and later was Chairman of the U.S. Delegation to the Seventh International Grasslands Conference in 1956. After leaving the Department of Agriculture in 1952, Dr. Myers became Head of the Department of Agronomy and Plant Genetics at the University of Minnesota. He became Dean of the Office of International Programs in 1963.
  Dr. Myers had been a consultant to The Rockefeller Foundation since 1954 and spent 1959-1960 in India in that capacity. As Associate Director of Agricultural Sciences in 1964 he also became Director of the International Institute of Tropical Agriculture in Ibadan from 1965-1967. With the Institute formally organized in 1968, he became Chairman of the Board. In 1967 Dr. Myers became Vice-President of the Foundation with interests in the areas of Medical and Natural Sciences, Agriculture, and programs oriented toward University Development, Population, Conquest of Hunger, and Quality of the Environment.
  Dr. Myers had many associations, some of which were Chairman, Committee on Agricultural Science, USDA; Chairman, Agricultural Research Facilities Needs Committee, USDA; Chairman, Latin American Science Board National Academy of Sciences; Member, U.S. National Commission, United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO); Consultant, Ford Foundation; Consultant, Office of Science and Technology, Executive Office of the President; Science Advisor to Assistant Administrator, Latin American Bureau, AID and Coordinator, Alliance for Progress, 1962; Member, U.S. Delegation to the United Nations Conference on Application of Science and Technology in Assistance to Developing Nations, 1963; Chairman, Crops Division, 1946, Vice President 1957, President 1958, American Society of Agronomy.
  Photographs
  - William M. Myers, Some have captions attached or typed on back, 1 with slight fading, some curling; 34 prints (Box 2, Folder 12)